Guide to the Widmer Wine Cellars Records,1906-1963.
Widmer Wine Cellars Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Widmer Wine Cellars Records, 1906-1963.
3141
Widmer Wine Cellars.
15.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, printed material, bills, statistics, accounts, alphabetical and subject files, photographs, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, printed material on equipment, bills and expenses, grape statistics, accounts with grape growers, alphabetical and subject files, photographs, and other material of the Widmer Wine Cellars, Naples, New York. Includes correspondence with numerous American producers of grapes and wine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, printed material on equipment, bills and expenses, grape statistics, accounts with grape growers, alphabetical and subject files, photographs, and other material of the Widmer Wine Cellars, Naples, New York. Includes correspondence with numerous American producers of grapes and wine.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Widmer Wine Cellars.
Subjects:
Viticulture.; Wine and wine making.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Ade, Carl C. Architect, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agriculture, Department of, 1952-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- Bardenherer's Wine Cellars, 1950-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Blue Prints, etc., 1932-1954 (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
- Brocton Wine Cellars, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Buchman & Buchman, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Grape Juice Advertising - Leaflet, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- City of New York Correspondence - Julius Wile Memo, 1940-1950, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Naples, New York - Canning Factory, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cook, Earl F., 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Italian Swiss Colony, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Wine Merchants, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- McGarrahan, Frank, 1940-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- New York Warehouse, 1942-1961 (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
- Inactive Brokers, 1941-1970 (Box 1, Folder 20-22)
- Out-dated Contracts, 1948-1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Contracts - Powell, 1949-1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Elggren, Paul, 1949-1955 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- MacGowen, James, 1941-1961 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
- Cooperage, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 27-28)
- Corning Glass works, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Corporation Trust Company, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- D'Inginni, Vincent - Case, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Employee Retirement, 1948-1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- FAA - Shipping Tabs - Disapproved, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Finger Lakes Wine Growers, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Fire Loss, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 35-37)
- Memos and Newspaper Articles re Cooperative Contracts, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Grape Juice Industry, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 39-41)
- Grape Juice - Customer Label, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Frozen Grape Juice Concentrate, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Grapes, 1945-1951 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Grape Seed Oil, 1930-1941 (Box 1, Folder 45-47)
- Historical, 1895, 1913, 1919, 1939, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Holland House Wine Company, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Holterbosch, Hans - New York City, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Inactive Brokers, 1939-1949 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Hail Claim, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Insurance, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 53-54)
- Jellies, Wine Sauce, etc., 1941-1953 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Department of Labor, 1939-1959 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Licenses, 1934-1955 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Miscellany, 1943-1954 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Puerto Rican Matters, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Rationing - Wines, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Riesling - Missouri, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Wine Articles, 1942-1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Tartrates, 1941-1955 (Box 2, Folder 2-5)
- Trucks - disposed of, 1936-1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Baron, John Melville - re New York State Wines, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Lawton Mackall - re. Varietal and Other Widmer Wines, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Wine Articles - New World Telegram and Sun, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Production of Wines, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The Squibb Institute, Harold Applegate - re. Widner Varietals, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- "Our Freedom's Blessings", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Machinery - Mayfield, 1906, 1919, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Maxfield Building, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous, 1942 48 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Montfort - Advertising, 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
- Montfort - Grape Juice and Jellies, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Montfort - Grape Juice Producers Association, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Montfort - Invoices, 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
- Montfort - Labels, 1933-1943 (Box 2, Folder 22-25)
- Montfort - Miscellaneous, 1934-1938 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
- Montfort - Permanent, 1937-1941 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
- Montfort - Reguatlion 7, 1935-1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Montfort - Regulation 698, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Montfort - States, 1935-1944 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Montfort - Trade Marks, 1930-1938 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- James Moroney, 1933-1939 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Old Controls, 1937-1951 (Box 2, Folder 35-37)
- Production Earnings, 1931-1945 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Photographs, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Price Lists, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Puerto Rican - Losses, 1937-1941 (Box 2, Folder 41-42)
- Puerto Rican - Old Accounts, 1935-1941 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Miscellaneous, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Cyclone Fence Company, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Prisoner of War Labor, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 46-50)
- Prisoner of War Camp - Bush Prefabricated Structure, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
- Prisoner of War Second Service Command, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
- Scrap Salvage, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- St. James Wine & Liquor [St. James Wines, Inc.), 1943 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Wine Sales, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Sforzini - Water Salvage, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Swartout & Rowdy, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Tidewater Warehouse, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Vineyard - Surveys, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Will Widmer, 1911-1913 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Wile, Julius Co., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- ABC Packaging Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Alsop Engineering Corporation, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Aluminum Seal Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Aluminum Company of America, 1943-1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- American Laundry Machinery Company, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- American Machinery Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Automataic Combustion, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- A - Equipment, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Barry-Wehmiller Machinery, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
- Bottling Machinery Sales Service Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- The Bump Pump Company, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 27)
- B - Equipment, 1935-1943 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Chamberlin Rubber Company, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Chisholm-Ryder Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Consolidated Packaging Machinery, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- C - Equipment, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- D - Equipment, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
- Detjen Corporation, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Edward Ermold Company, 1944-1947 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Ertel Engineering Corporation, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- E - Equipment, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- J. L. Ferguson Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- First Machinery Corporation, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Fischer & Porter Company, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- F - Equipment, 1943-1947 (Box 3, Folder 42-43)
- Genesee Heating, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Gorndt Machine Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Gross Machinery Company, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- G - Equipment, 1943-1950 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Hickey-Freeman Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Huntley Manufacturing Company, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- H - Equipment, 1943-1954 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Industrial Filter and Pump Manucacturing Company, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 51)
- I - Equipment, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Jelly Machinery, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- [Winery Records], 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 54-55)
- J - Equipment, 1944, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 56)
- K - Equipment, 1919, 1943,n.d. (Box 3, Folder 57)
- John Gaylord Lowe Company, 1947-50 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- L - Equipment, 1943, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 59)
- M, N Miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Mollenberg-Betz Machine Company, 1945-1950 (Box 3, Folder 61-62)
- Morris Machine Works - Lester E. Mosher, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 63)
- M - Equipment, 1937-1952 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Mojonnier Bros. Co., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- New Jersey Machine Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Niagara Filter Corporation, 1943-1947 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- N - Equipment, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- O - Equipment, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pfaudler Co., 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
- Perry Equipment Co., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Pneumatic Scale Corporation, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
- Pomona Machine Works, 1946-1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Priorities - War Production Board, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
- P - Equipment, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Q - Equipment, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Rapids-Standard Co., Inc., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Reeves Pulley Co., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Refrigeration Equipment, 1941-1944 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Republic Filters, Inc., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Root, Neal & Co., 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- R - Equipment, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sforzini, Lewis J., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Sub-Station, 1933-1944 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- S - Equipment, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
- Tite-Cap Machine, Inc., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Tri-Clover Machine Co., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- T - Equipment, 1933-1943 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- U - Equipment, 1934-1944 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- W - Equipment, 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Valley Foundry and Machine Works, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Alcohol, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Alcohol Tax Unit, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 31-34)
- American Grape Juice Corp., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- American Machine & Metal Manufacturing Corporation, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- American Surety, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Alsop Engineering Corp., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Aluminum Company of America, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- B, 1935-1937 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Baldwin & Strachan Inc., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- E. C. Bock, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Britt-McKinney; Britt-Johnson; Britt-Shiver-Norcom, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Calkin & Co., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 44-45)
- Canners' Exchange, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- C. & E. Grape Growers Co-Operative, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Harry B. Cook, Inc., 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- LeRoy W. Crowder, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Dun's Winery Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Eastern Wine Growers Association, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Finger Lakes Wine Growers Association, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 52-54)
- G, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Giron & Torres - Brokerage Statement, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- H, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- J, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- K, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Leventis, P.P. & Co., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- M, 1934-1936 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- L.M. Martini Grape Products, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Mason, Fenwick & Lawrence, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Michigan, State of, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- James Moroney - Brokerage Statements, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Montfort, L. B. Jan.-Mar., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Montfort Apr.-July, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Montfort Aug.-Oct., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Montfort Nov.-Dec., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- National testing Laboratories, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
- Naples Grape Growers, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- New York (Geneva) Department of Agriculture, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- New York State ABC Board, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- New York State Department of Taxation, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- O, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- P, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Pamphlets and Clippings, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
- Pennsylvania, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 18-19)
- Charles H. Platter - Brokerage Statements, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- R, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- S, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- United States Federal Alcohol Administration, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- United States Congress, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- U, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Utica Mutual Insurance Co., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- V, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- W, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- West Virginia Liquor Control Commission, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- H. R. Wrasse, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- re Flash Pasteurizer purchased from Corning Glass, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- A, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Aparicio Hermanos, Sucrs., 1933-1937 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- B, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Brokers, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- J. L. Buchman - Hebrew National Grape, et al, 1926-1957 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- C, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Cook, Harry B. Inc., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Crowder, LeRoy, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- D, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Ferguson-Bedell, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Finger Lakes Wine Growers Association, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Geron & Torres, Sucr., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- H, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- The Kennedy Menke Co., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- L, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Labels, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- M, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Martini, L. M., 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Moroney, James, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Montfort, Louis B., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 51-52)
- N, 1037 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- P, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Pennsylvania Liquor Control Board, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Pennsylvania (Sales Analyses), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Pamphlets, Wine Lists, etc., ca. 1937 (Box 5, Folder 57-58)
- Pomace, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Price Lists, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- R, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- S, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- T, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- United States, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- United States Federal Alcohol Administration - Alcohol Tax Unit, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- United States - Protests to Federal Alcohol Administration, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- V, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- W, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- A, 1937-1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- B, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- C, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- D, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- E, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- F, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- G, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- H, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- J, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- K, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- L, 1936-1939 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- M, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Martini, L. M., 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- N, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- P, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- R, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- S, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- T, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- U, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- W, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
- Aetna Life Insurance, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Internal Revenue Department, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- A - Italian Swiss, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- J - Lehigh Valley Railroad Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Martini, L. M., 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- M - No, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Naples, Village of, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- New York Central Electric, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- New York Office Expense, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- P - Z, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- A - Carey, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Cars Purchased, 1937-1941 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Internal Revenue Department, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- D - Italian Swiss, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- J - Nixon, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Naples Taxes, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- New York Central Electric, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- New York Office Expense, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 39-40)
- P - Taylor, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Wine and Brandy Purchases, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- A - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Lohr - Expense, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- M - New York State Electric, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- New York Office Expense, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- P - Z, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Swartout & Rowley, 1943-1947 (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
- A - Z, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
- A - M, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 52-53)
- N - W, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 54-55)
- Payables A - F, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 56-57)
- Payables Ha - Sh, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- S - Z, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Payables A - Z, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Alvey Manufacturing Company, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Barry-Wehmiller Machinery Company, 1919-1920 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Beals McCarthy & Rogers, 1934-1936 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- B - Br, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Bolles Hardware, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Bro - Bz, 1934-1936 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Budde & Westermann, 1933-1936 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Ca - Cn, 1933-1936 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Canners Exchange Subscribers, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Philip Carey Company, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Clyde Cooperage Company, 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Co - Cz, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Creamery Package Manufacturing Company, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Crown Cork & Seal Company (The), 1933-1935 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- D, 1919-1936 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Dansville Pipe & Supply Company, 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Dunning & Boschert Press Co., Inc., 1920-1935 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- E, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Economic Machinery Company, 1919-1936 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- F, 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Forster, John M. Company, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Ga - Gn, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Go - Gz, 1919-1936 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Ha - Hd, 1924-1936 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Hall, H. B., 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Haverstick & Company, Inc., 1932-1936 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
- Haverstick & acompany, Inc., 1918-1921 (Box 7, Folder 20-22)
- He - Hn, 1919-1936 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Henes & Keller Company, 1918-1934 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Ho - Hz, 1919-1935 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- I, 1919-1936 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- J, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Johns-Manville, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- K, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Ka - Lh, 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Lefler, Harry, 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Li - Lz, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Chapman Accounts (starting estimate(, 1955-1958, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Emerson Accounts, 1955-1958, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Underwood Accounts, 1955-1958, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Lical Accounts, 1955-1958, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 36-37)
- Chapman Accounts (starting 1955), 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Standish Accounts, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- All Accounts, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Emerson Accounts, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Chapman Accounts, 1949-1951 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Underwood Accounts, 1949-1951 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Widmer Local Accounts, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Standish Accounts, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Standish Accounts, 1949-1955 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Monthly Cost Sheets - Jan.-June, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Monthly Cost Sheets - July-Dec., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Monthly Cost Sheets - Jan.-June, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Monthly Cost Sheets - July-Dec., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Monthly Cost Sheets - Jan.-June, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Monthly Cost Sheets - July-Dec., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Price Lists, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Monopoly States and Others - Puerto Rico, 1936-1959 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- New Wine Production, 1945-1951 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- G. J. & Wine Shipments, 1933-1956 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Costa Rica - Export - Dominican Republic, Panama, Jamaica, Venezuela, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Total Sales, 1933-1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Distribution of Sales, 1935-1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Sales and Commissions, 1939-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Wage Summaries - Employee Insurance, 1936-1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Price Comparisons, 1932-1952 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Commissions and Trucking, 1939-1952 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Unit Costs, 1939-1953 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Grape Costs by Buyers, 1939-1953 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Tonnage by Buyers, 1939-1954 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Seasonal Operations, 1938-1953 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Operating Costs, 1939-1953 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Widmer Crops, 1917-1949 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Monthly Costs Jan.-June, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Monthly Costs July-Dec., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Production Costs Summary, 1948-1950 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Monthly cost Sheets Jan.-Apr., 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Monthly Cost Sheets May-Aug., 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Monthly Cost Sheets Sept.-Dec., 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Widmer Vineyards - Cash profit and loss, 1950-1956 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Grapes, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Old Grape Book, 1946-1951 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Grape Book, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Grape Book, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Grapes - Juice, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Grape Juice, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Grape Growers Information, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Bunch counts and Estimates, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Grape Juice Requirements, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Grape Estimates and Totals, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Grape Juice, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Grape Estimates, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Grape Juice, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Grapes, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Grape Estimates and Bunch Count, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Grape Estimates and Bunch Count, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Grapes, Contracts, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Tray Record, ca. 1960 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Pressing, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Grapes, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Booklets, etc., re Wine, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Wine Lists, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- A, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- B, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- C, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- J. Bernard Edmonds, M. A., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Barry Wehmiller, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Canton Barrel & Bag, Inc., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Connecticut, State of, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Leroy W. Crowder - Brokerage, 1938, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Department of Taxation, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- District of Columbia, Government of, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Elggren Bros., Utah, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Finger Lakes Wine Grower, 1944-1948 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Gould Pumps, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Greig, Lawrence & Hoyt, Ltd., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- H, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- I, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- F. Korbel & Bros., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- M, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Mason, Fenwick & Lawrence, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- N, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- New York State Cornell Bulletins, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Ohio, State of, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Owens, Charles L., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Owens-Illinois Glass, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- P, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
- Pfaudler Company, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 31-33)
- R, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- S, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Sforzini, Lewis J., 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 36-37)
- Shriver Filter Co., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- T, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Brands, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 40-41)
- United States C ongress - Washington, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Urbana Wine Co., 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Utica Mutual Insurance Co., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- W, 1925, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Walker-Wallaace, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Warner, Lansing B., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Wendnagel & Co., 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Widmer, Will, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- A, 1919, 1931-1935 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Advertising, Promotion - Radio, etc., 1931-1935 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- B, 1931-1934 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Bulletins - Bills, etc. (USA), 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- C, 1921, 1925, 1928, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Certificate of Registration - Licenses and Permits, 1933-1936 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1933, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Harry B. Cook, Inc., 1934-1936 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- D, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- R. G. Dun & Co., 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- E, 1933-1935 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- F, 1933-1935 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Form Letters, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 62)